document.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', () => {
  const levels = [
    // Define levels with their questions and answers here
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üç≠üç≠ + üç≠üç≠üç≠ =', answer: '5' },
        { question: 'üç´üç´üç´üç´ + üç´üç´ =', answer: '6' },
        { question: 'ü•öü•ö + ü•ö =', answer: '3' },
        { question: 'üçîüçîüçî - üçîüçî =', answer: '1' },
        { question: 'üç¶üç¶üç¶üç¶üç¶üç¶ - üç¶üç¶ =', answer: '4' },
      ],
      answers: ['1', '3', '5', '4', '6', '2', '7', '9'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üçâüçâüçâ - üçâ =', answer: '2' },
        { question: 'üçãüçãüçãüçã + üçã =', answer: '5' },
        { question: 'üçÖüçÖ + üçÖ =', answer: '3' },
        { question: 'ü•ë - ü•ë =', answer: '0' },
        { question: 'üçÜüçÜüçÜ - üçÜüçÜ =', answer: '1' },
      ],
      answers: ['1', '3', '5', '0', '2', '4', '7', '9'],
    },   
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üìóüìò + üìóüìòüìóüìò =', answer: '6' },
        { question: '‚úè‚úè‚úè - ‚úè‚úè‚úè =', answer: '0' },
        { question: 'üìèüìèüìèüìè / üìèüìè =', answer: '2' },
        { question: 'üéíüéíüéí * üéíüéí =', answer: '6' },
        { question: 'üìêüìê - üìê =', answer: '1' },
      ],
      answers: ['1', '3', '5', '0', '2', '6', '6', '9'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üê´üê´üê´ + üê´üê´üê´üê´ =', answer: '7' },
        { question: 'üêéüêéüêéüêéüêéüêéüêé + üêéüêéüêéüêé =', answer: '11' },
        { question: 'üêë + üêëüêëüêëüêë =', answer: '5' },
        { question: 'üêòüêòüêòüêòüêò + üêòüêòüêòüêòüêò =', answer: '10' },
        { question: 'üêíüêíüêí + üêí =', answer: '4' },
      ],
      answers: ['11', '7', '5', '0', '4', '6', '10', '19'],
    },   
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üêüüêüüêüüêü - üêüüêüüêü =', answer: '1' },
        { question: 'üê¨üê¨ - üê¨üê¨üê¨üê¨ =', answer: '-2' },
        { question: 'üêôüêôüêôüêôüêôüêô - üêôüêôüêôüêôüêô =', answer: '1' },
        { question: 'üê≥üê≥üê≥ - üê≥üê≥üê≥üê≥üê≥üê≥ =', answer: '-3' },
        { question: 'üêúüêúüêúüêú + üêúüêú =', answer: '6' },
      ],
      answers: ['1', '7', '-3', '-2', '4', '6', '1', '10'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üå¥üå¥üå¥ * üå¥üå¥üå¥üå¥ =', answer: '12' },
        { question: '‚òòÔ∏è‚òòÔ∏è * ‚òòÔ∏è‚òòÔ∏è =', answer: '4' },
        { question: 'üçÇüçÇüçÇüçÇ * üçÇüçÇ =', answer: '8' },
        { question: 'üå∑üå∑üå∑üå∑ * üå∑üå∑üå∑ =', answer: '12' },
        { question: 'üåµüåµ / üåµüåµ =', answer: '1' },
      ],
      answers: ['12', '7', '-3', '12', '4', '8', '1', '0'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üçëüçëüçëüçë / üçëüçëüçëüçë =', answer: '1' },
        { question: 'üçáüçáüçáüçáüçáüçá / üçáüçáüçá =', answer: '2' },
        { question: 'üçÜüçÜ / üçÜüçÜ =', answer: '1' },
        { question: 'üçåüçåüçåüçå / üçåüçå =', answer: '2' },
        { question: 'üåΩüåΩ * üåΩüåΩüåΩüåΩüåΩ =', answer: '10' },
      ],
      answers: ['1', '2', '1', '2', '4', '9', '10', '0'],
    },  
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üç¨üç¨ + üç¨üç¨üç¨ + üç¨üç¨ =', answer: '7' },
        { question: 'üç©üç©üç© + üç©üç© + üç© =', answer: '6' },
        { question: 'üéÇüéÇ / üéÇüéÇ =', answer: '1' },
        { question: 'üç∞ + üç∞üç∞ + üç∞üç∞üç∞ =', answer: '6' },
        { question: 'üçßüçß - üçßüçßüçß =', answer: '-1' },
      ],
      answers: ['1', '7', '1', '2', '6', '-1', '6', '0'],
    },  
    {
      questions: [
        { question: '‚öΩÔ∏è‚öΩÔ∏è‚öΩÔ∏è + ‚öΩÔ∏è‚öΩÔ∏è =', answer: '5' },
        { question: '‚öæÔ∏è‚öæÔ∏è‚öæÔ∏è‚öæÔ∏è - ‚öæÔ∏è‚öæÔ∏è =', answer: '2' },
        { question: '‚ôü‚ôü‚ôü‚ôü‚ôü‚ôü / ‚ôü‚ôü =', answer: '3' },
        { question: 'üèÜüèÜ + üèÜüèÜ + üèÜüèÜüèÜ =', answer: '7' },
        { question: '‚õ≥Ô∏è‚õ≥Ô∏è‚õ≥Ô∏è * ‚õ≥Ô∏è‚õ≥Ô∏è‚õ≥Ô∏è‚õ≥Ô∏è =', answer: '12' },
      ],
      answers: ['5', '7', '1', '2', '3', '12', '6', '0'],
    },  
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üöÄüöÄ * üöÄüöÄ * üöÄüöÄ =', answer: '8' },
        { question: '‚úàÔ∏è‚úàÔ∏è - ‚úàÔ∏è‚úàÔ∏è‚úàÔ∏è‚úàÔ∏è =', answer: '-2' },
        { question: 'üö≤üö≤ + üö≤üö≤ * üö≤ =', answer: '4' },
        { question: 'üöôüöôüöô + üöô + üöôüöô =', answer: '6' },
        { question: 'üö¢ * üö¢üö¢ + üö¢üö¢ =', answer: '4' },
      ],
      answers: ['4', '8', '1', '-2', '2', '4', '6', '5'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üóºüóº * üóºüóºüóº + üöÄüöÄ =', answer: '8' },
        { question: 'üé°üé° + ‚úàÔ∏è‚úàÔ∏è‚úàÔ∏è‚úàÔ∏è =', answer: '6' },
        { question: '‚öìÔ∏è‚öìÔ∏è‚öìÔ∏è - ‚öìÔ∏è‚öìÔ∏è * üöô =', answer: '1' },
        { question: '‚õµÔ∏è‚õµÔ∏è‚õµÔ∏è‚õµÔ∏è + üöô * ‚õµÔ∏è‚õµÔ∏è =', answer: '6' },
        { question: 'üíâ - üíâüíâüíâüíâüíâüíâüíâ =', answer: '-6' },
      ],
      answers: ['6', '8', '1', '-6', '-6', '-1', '6', '7'],
    },  
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üöÄüöÄ + üç¨üç¨üç¨ + ‚öìÔ∏è‚öìÔ∏è =', answer: '7' },
        { question: 'üöôüöôüöô + üç©üç© + ‚úàÔ∏è =', answer: '6' },
        { question: 'üéÇüéÇ / üç∞üç∞ =', answer: '1' },
        { question: 'üö¢ + ‚õµÔ∏è‚õµÔ∏è + üöôüöôüöô =', answer: '6' },
        { question: 'üç¨üç¨ - üçßüçßüçß =', answer: '-1' },
      ],
      answers: ['1', '7', '1', '2', '6', '-1', '6', '0'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üêüüêüüêüüêü - ‚öΩÔ∏è‚öΩÔ∏è‚öΩÔ∏è =', answer: '1' },
        { question: 'üçÇüçÇ - üê¨üê¨üê¨üê¨ =', answer: '-2' },
        { question: 'üêôüêôüêôüêôüêôüêô - üçëüçëüçëüçëüçë =', answer: '1' },
        { question: 'üê≥üê≥üê≥ - üê≥üê≥üê≥üê≥üê≥üê≥ =', answer: '-3' },
        { question: 'üêúüêúüêúüêú + üêúüêú =', answer: '6' },
      ],
      answers: ['1', '7', '-3', '-2', '4', '6', '1', '10'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üöÄüöÄ * üèÜüèÜ * ‚öΩÔ∏è‚öΩÔ∏è =', answer: '8' },
        { question: '‚úàÔ∏è‚úàÔ∏è - ‚úàÔ∏è‚úàÔ∏è‚úàÔ∏è‚úàÔ∏è =', answer: '-2' },
        { question: 'üçåüçå + üö≤üö≤ * üêí =', answer: '4' },
        { question: 'üöôüöôüöô + üöô + üçÖüçÖ =', answer: '6' },
        { question: 'üö¢ * üêòüêò + üö¢üö¢ =', answer: '4' },
      ],
      answers: ['5', '8', '1', '-2', '2', '4', '6', '4'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: '‚Ö° + ‚Ö¢ =', answer: '5' },
        { question: '‚Ö£ + ‚Ö° =', answer: '6' },
        { question: '‚Öß + ‚Ö§ =', answer: '13' },
        { question: '‚Ö® - ‚Ö¢ =', answer: '6' },
        { question: '‚Ö¶ - ‚Ö° =', answer: '5' },
      ],
      answers: ['1', '13', '5', '4', '6', '2', '6', '5'],
    },  
    {
      questions: [
        { question: '‚Ö© - ‚Ö° =', answer: '8' },
        { question: '‚Ö™ + ‚Ö† =', answer: '12' },
        { question: '‚Ö¢ + ‚Ö¢ =', answer: '6' },
        { question: '‚Öß - ‚Öß =', answer: '0' },
        { question: '‚Ö¶ - ‚Ö• =', answer: '1' },
      ],
      answers: ['1', '3', '6', '0', '12', '4', '8', '9'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üå¥üå¥üå¥ * ‚Ö£ =', answer: '12' },
        { question: '‚Ö° * ‚òòÔ∏è‚òòÔ∏è =', answer: '4' },
        { question: '‚Ö£ * üçÇüçÇ =', answer: '8' },
        { question: 'üå∑üå∑üå∑üå∑ * ‚Ö¢ =', answer: '12' },
        { question: '‚Ö° / üåµüåµ =', answer: '1' },
      ],
      answers: ['12', '7', '-3', '12', '4', '8', '1', '0'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: '‚Ö° + ‚Ö¢ + ‚Ö° =', answer: '7' },
        { question: '‚Ö¢ + ‚Ö° + ‚Ö† =', answer: '6' },
        { question: '‚Ö° / ‚Ö° =', answer: '1' },
        { question: '‚Ö† + ‚Ö° + ‚Ö¢ =', answer: '6' },
        { question: '‚Ö° - ‚Ö¢ =', answer: '-1' },
      ],
      answers: ['1', '7', '1', '2', '6', '-1', '6', '0'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üóºüóº * ‚Ö¢ + üöÄüöÄ =', answer: '8' },
        { question: 'üé°üé° + ‚Ö£ =', answer: '6' },
        { question: '‚öìÔ∏è‚öìÔ∏è‚öìÔ∏è - ‚Ö° * üöô =', answer: '1' },
        { question: '‚Ö£ + üöô * ‚õµÔ∏è‚õµÔ∏è =', answer: '6' },
        { question: 'üíâ - ‚Ö¶ =', answer: '-6' },
      ],
      answers: ['6', '8', '1', '-6', '-6', '-1', '6', '7'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: '‚Ö° * ‚Ö§ =', answer: '‚Ö©' },
        { question: '‚Ö¢ * ‚Ö¢ =', answer: '‚Ö®' },
        { question: '‚Ö§ * ‚Ö£ =', answer: '‚Ö©‚Ö©' },
        { question: '‚Ö£ * ‚Ö† =', answer: '‚Ö£' },
        { question: '‚Ö† * ‚Ö° =', answer: '‚Ö°' },
      ],
      answers: ['‚Ö°', '‚Ö®', '-‚Öß', '‚Ö©', '‚Ö©‚Ö©', '‚Ö£', '‚Ö§', '0'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: '‚Ö£ - ‚Ö¢ =', answer: '‚Ö†' },
        { question: '‚Ö° - ‚Ö£ =', answer: '-‚Ö°' },
        { question: '‚Ö• - ‚Ö§ =', answer: '‚Ö†' },
        { question: '‚Ö¢ - ‚Ö• =', answer: '-‚Ö¢' },
        { question: '‚Ö£ + ‚Ö° =', answer: '‚Ö•' },
      ],
      answers: ['‚Ö†', '‚Ö¢', '-‚Ö¢', '-‚Ö°', '‚Ö°', '‚Ö•', '‚Ö†', '‚Ö©'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: '‚Ö£ / ‚Ö£ =', answer: '‚Ö†' },
        { question: '‚Ö• / ‚Ö¢ =', answer: '‚Ö°' },
        { question: '‚Ö° / ‚Ö° =', answer: '‚Ö†' },
        { question: '‚Ö£ / ‚Ö° =', answer: '‚Ö°' },
        { question: '‚Ö° * ‚Ö§ =', answer: '‚Ö©' },
      ],
      answers: ['‚Ö†', '‚Ö°', '‚Ö†', '‚Ö°', '‚Ö£', '-‚Ö°', '‚Ö©', '‚Ö©‚Ö©'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: '‚öΩÔ∏è‚öΩÔ∏è‚öΩÔ∏è + ‚Ö° =', answer: '‚Ö§' },
        { question: '‚Ö£ - ‚öæÔ∏è‚öæÔ∏è =', answer: '‚Ö°' },
        { question: '‚Ö• / ‚ôü‚ôü =', answer: '‚Ö¢' },
        { question: 'üèÜüèÜ + üèÜüèÜ + ‚Ö¢ =', answer: '‚Ö¶' },
        { question: '‚Ö¢ * ‚õ≥Ô∏è‚õ≥Ô∏è‚õ≥Ô∏è‚õ≥Ô∏è =', answer: '‚Ö´' },
      ],
      answers: ['‚Ö§', '‚Ö¶', '‚Ö®', '‚Ö°', '‚Ö¢', '‚Ö´', '‚Ö©', '0'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: '‚ë° + ‚ë¢ =', answer: '5' },
        { question: '‚ë£ + ‚ë° =', answer: '6' },
        { question: '‚ëß + ‚ë§ =', answer: '13' },
        { question: '‚ë® - ‚ë¢ =', answer: '6' },
        { question: '‚ë¶ - ‚ë° =', answer: '5' },
      ],
      answers: ['1', '13', '5', '4', '6', '2', '6', '9'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: '‚ë£ - ‚ë¢ =', answer: '1' },
        { question: '‚ë° - ‚ë£ =', answer: '-2' },
        { question: '‚ë• - ‚ë§ =', answer: '1' },
        { question: '‚ë¢ - ‚ë• =', answer: '-3' },
        { question: '‚ë£ + ‚ë° =', answer: '6' },
      ],
      answers: ['1', '7', '-3', '-2', '4', '6', '1', '10'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: '‚ë¢ * ‚ë£ =', answer: '12' },
        { question: '‚ë° * ‚ë° =', answer: '4' },
        { question: '‚ë£ * ‚ë¢ =', answer: '12' },
        { question: '‚ë° / ‚ë° =', answer: '1' },
        { question: '‚ë£ * ‚ë° =', answer: '8' },
      ],
      answers: ['12', '7', '-3', '12', '4', '8', '1', '0'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üçëüçëüçëüçë / üçëüçëüçëüçë =', answer: '1' },
        { question: 'üçáüçáüçáüçáüçáüçá / üçáüçáüçá =', answer: '2' },
        { question: 'üçÜüçÜ / üçÜüçÜ =', answer: '1' },
        { question: 'üçåüçåüçåüçå / üçåüçå =', answer: '2' },
        { question: 'üåΩüåΩ * üåΩüåΩüåΩüåΩüåΩ =', answer: '10' },
      ],
      answers: ['1', '2', '1', '2', '4', '9', '10', '0'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: '‚ë° + üóºüóºüóº + üöÄüöÄ =', answer: '7' },
        { question: '‚õµÔ∏è‚õµÔ∏è‚õµÔ∏è‚õµÔ∏è + ‚ë† + ‚õµÔ∏è =', answer: '6' },
        { question: 'üé°üé° + ‚ë£ =', answer: '6' },
        { question: '‚ë† - üíâüíâüíâüíâüíâüíâüíâ =', answer: '-6' },
        { question: '‚öìÔ∏è‚öìÔ∏è‚öìÔ∏è - ‚ë° * üöô =', answer: '1' },
      ],
      answers: ['6', '8', '1', '-6', '-6', '-1', '6', '7'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üöôüöôüöô + ‚ë† + ‚Ö° =', answer: '6' },
        { question: '‚ë° * ‚Ö° * ‚öΩÔ∏è‚öΩÔ∏è =', answer: '8' },
        { question: 'üçåüçå + üö≤üö≤ * ‚Ö† =', answer: '4' },
        { question: '‚úàÔ∏è‚úàÔ∏è - ‚úàÔ∏è‚úàÔ∏è‚úàÔ∏è‚úàÔ∏è =', answer: '-2' },
        { question: '‚Ö† * üêòüêò + ‚ë° =', answer: '4' },
      ],
      answers: ['5', '8', '1', '-2', '2', '4', '6', '4'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: '‚Ö£ + üéÉüéÉ + ‚ë¢ =', answer: '‚Ö®' },
        { question: '‚ò†Ô∏è‚ò†Ô∏è * ‚ë• * ‚Ö† =', answer: '‚Ö´' },
        { question: 'üëøüëøüëø + ‚ì™ * ‚Ö† =', answer: '‚Ö¢' },
        { question: '‚Ö© - üëªüëª =', answer: '‚Öß' },
        { question: '‚Ö§ * üë∂üë∂ + ‚ë° =', answer: '‚Ö´' },
      ],
      answers: ['‚Ö´', '‚Öß', '‚Ö†', '‚Ö¢', '‚Ö®', '‚Ö´', '‚Ö£', '‚Ö§'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üòéüòé + üòúüòú + üòãüòã + üòÅüòÅ =', answer: '8' },
        { question: 'üëä * üôåüôå * üë∂üë∂ * üëâ =', answer: '4' },
        { question: 'üëµüëµüëµüëµ / üë¥üë¥ =', answer: '2' },
        { question: 'üíÉ + üíÉüíÉ + üíÉüíÉüíÉ + üíÉüíÉüíÉüíÉ =', answer: '10' },
        { question: 'üèÉüèÉ * üèÉüèÉ * üèÉüèÉ  =', answer: '8' },
      ],
      answers: ['10', '8', '1', '8', '2', '4', '6', '5'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üíºüíº + üåÇüåÇüåÇ + ‚òÇÔ∏è‚òÇÔ∏è =', answer: '7' },
        { question: 'üíÑüíÑüíÑ + üíçüíç + üë† =', answer: '6' },
        { question: 'üêßüêß - üêåüêåüêå =', answer: '-1' },
        { question: 'üêç + ‚õµÔ∏è‚õµÔ∏è + üêçüêçüêç =', answer: '6' },
        { question: 'üêùüêù / üêóüêó =', answer: '1' },
      ],
      answers: ['1', '7', '1', '2', '6', '-1', '6', '0'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üê´üê´ * üéÑüéÑüéÑüéÑüéÑ =', answer: '10' },
        { question: 'üçÑüçÑüçÑüçÑ / üçÅüçÅüçÅüçÅ =', answer: '1' },
        { question: 'üî•üî• / üí•üí• =', answer: '1' },
        { question: '‚≠êÔ∏è‚≠êÔ∏è‚≠êÔ∏è‚≠êÔ∏è‚≠êÔ∏è‚≠êÔ∏è / üçáüçáüçá =', answer: '2' },
        { question: '‚òÇÔ∏è‚òÇÔ∏è‚òÇÔ∏è‚òÇÔ∏è / üçéüçé =', answer: '2' },
      ],
      answers: ['1', '2', '1', '2', '4', '9', '10', '0'],
    },  
    {
      questions: [
        { question: '3 + üççüççüçç + ‚Ö° + ‚ë£ =', answer: '12' },
        { question: 'üçûüçû * ‚Ö¢ * 11 * ‚ì™ =', answer: '0' },
        { question: 'üçìüçìüçìüçìüçìüçìüçìüçìüçì / ‚Ö¢ =', answer: '3' },
        { question: '‚Ö¥ + ‚ì™ + 6 + üçîüçî =', answer: '13' },
        { question: 'üçïüçïüçï * ‚ë§ * ‚Ö†  =', answer: '15' },
      ],
      answers: ['12', '8', '1', '3', '13', '4', '15', '0'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
      { question: '‚õµÔ∏è‚õµÔ∏è‚õµÔ∏è‚õµÔ∏è + üöô * ‚õµÔ∏è‚õµÔ∏è =', answer: '10' },
        { question: 'üóºüóº * üóºüóºüóº + üöÄüöÄ =', answer: '8' },
        { question: '‚öìÔ∏è‚öìÔ∏è‚öìÔ∏è - ‚öìÔ∏è‚öìÔ∏è - üöô =', answer: '0' },
        { question: 'üé°üé° + ‚úàÔ∏è‚úàÔ∏è‚úàÔ∏è‚úàÔ∏è =', answer: '6' },
        { question: 'üíâ - üíâüíâüíâüíâüíâüíâüíâ =', answer: '-6' },
      ],
      answers: ['6', '10', '1', '-6', '8', '-1', '6', '0'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üóºüóº * ‚Ö¢ + üöÄüöÄ =', answer: '8' },
        { question: 'üé°üé° + ‚Ö£ =', answer: '6' },
        { question: '‚öìÔ∏è‚öìÔ∏è‚öìÔ∏è - ‚Ö° * üöô =', answer: '1' },
        { question: '‚Ö£ + üöô * ‚õµÔ∏è‚õµÔ∏è =', answer: '6' },
        { question: 'üíâ - ‚Ö¶ =', answer: '-6' },
      ],
      answers: ['6', '8', '1', '-6', '-6', '-1', '6', '7'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üóºüóº * üóºüóºüóº + üöÄüöÄ =', answer: '8' },
        { question: 'üé°üé° + ‚úàÔ∏è‚úàÔ∏è‚úàÔ∏è‚úàÔ∏è =', answer: '6' },
        { question: '‚öìÔ∏è‚öìÔ∏è‚öìÔ∏è - ‚öìÔ∏è‚öìÔ∏è * üöô =', answer: '1' },
        { question: '‚õµÔ∏è‚õµÔ∏è‚õµÔ∏è‚õµÔ∏è + üöô * ‚õµÔ∏è‚õµÔ∏è =', answer: '6' },
        { question: 'üíâ - üíâüíâüíâüíâüíâüíâüíâ =', answer: '-6' },
      ],
      answers: ['6', '8', '1', '-6', '-6', '-1', '6', '7'],
    },  
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üöÄüöÄ + üç¨üç¨üç¨ + ‚öìÔ∏è‚öìÔ∏è =', answer: '7' },
        { question: 'üöôüöôüöô + üç©üç© + ‚úàÔ∏è =', answer: '6' },
        { question: 'üéÇüéÇ / üç∞üç∞ =', answer: '1' },
        { question: 'üö¢ + ‚õµÔ∏è‚õµÔ∏è + üöôüöôüöô =', answer: '6' },
        { question: 'üç¨üç¨ - üçßüçßüçß =', answer: '-1' },
      ],
      answers: ['1', '7', '1', '2', '6', '-1', '6', '0'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üå¥üå¥üå¥ * üå¥üå¥üå¥üå¥ =', answer: '12' },
        { question: '‚òòÔ∏è‚òòÔ∏è * ‚òòÔ∏è‚òòÔ∏è =', answer: '4' },
        { question: 'üçÇüçÇüçÇüçÇ * üçÇüçÇ =', answer: '8' },
        { question: 'üå∑üå∑üå∑üå∑ * üå∑üå∑üå∑ =', answer: '12' },
        { question: 'üåµüåµ / üåµüåµ =', answer: '1' },
      ],
      answers: ['12', '7', '-3', '12', '4', '8', '1', '0'],
    },
    {
      questions: [
        { question: 'üçëüçëüçëüçë / üçëüçëüçëüçë =', answer: '1' },
        { question: 'üçáüçáüçáüçáüçáüçá / üçáüçáüçá =', answer: '2' },
        { question: 'üçÜüçÜ / üçÜüçÜ =', answer: '1' },
        { question: 'üçåüçåüçåüçå / üçåüçå =', answer: '2' },
        { question: 'üåΩüåΩ * üåΩüåΩüåΩüåΩüåΩ =', answer: '10' },
      ],
      answers: ['1', '2', '1', '2', '4', '9', '10', '0'],
    }, 
    // Add more levels here as needed
  ];

  let currentLevel = 0;
  let correctAnswersCount = 0;
  let currentQuestionIndex = 0;

  let touchStartPosition = { x: 0, y: 0 };
  let currentDraggedElement = null;

  function getTouchPosition(event) {
    return {
      x: event.touches[0].clientX,
      y: event.touches[0].clientY
    };
  }

  const questionContainer = document.getElementById('question-container');
  const answerContainer = document.getElementById('answer-container');
  const nextLevelButton = document.getElementById('next-level-button');
  const levelTextElement = document.getElementById('level-text');

  // Create audio elements for sound effects
  const matchSound = new Audio("SFX/match_sound.mp3");
  const nonMatchSound = new Audio("SFX/non_match_sound.mp3");

    const tryLeftElement = document.getElementById('tryleft');
  const tryAgainButton = document.getElementById('Try-Again-button');

  let triesRemaining = 3;

  // Preload the audio files
  matchSound.preload = "auto";
  nonMatchSound.preload = "auto";
  matchSound.load();
  nonMatchSound.load();

function initLevel() {
  const level = levels[currentLevel];
  const questions = level.questions;
  const answers = level.answers;

  correctAnswersCount = 0;

  questionContainer.innerHTML = '';
  answerContainer.innerHTML = '';

  questions.forEach((question, index) => {
    const questionDiv = document.createElement('div');
    questionDiv.classList.add('question');
    questionContainer.appendChild(questionDiv);

    const parts = question.question.split(/(\s+)/).filter((e) => e.trim().length > 0);

    parts.forEach((part) => {
      if (isOperator(part)) {
        const operatorSpan = document.createElement('span');
        operatorSpan.classList.add('operator');
        operatorSpan.textContent = part;
        questionDiv.appendChild(operatorSpan);
      } else {
        const operandSpan = document.createElement('span');
        operandSpan.textContent = part;
        questionDiv.appendChild(operandSpan);
      }
    });

    const dropField = document.createElement('div');
    dropField.classList.add('drop-field');
    dropField.setAttribute('data-answer', question.answer);
    dropField.textContent = '___';
    questionDiv.appendChild(dropField);
  });

  shuffleArray(answers);
  answers.forEach((answer, index) => {
    const draggableAnswer = document.createElement('div');
    draggableAnswer.textContent = answer;
    draggableAnswer.classList.add('answer');
    draggableAnswer.setAttribute('data-value', answer);
    draggableAnswer.draggable = true;

    draggableAnswer.addEventListener('dragstart', dragStart);
    answerContainer.appendChild(draggableAnswer);
  });
}

function isOperator(part) {
  return /[-+*/=]/.test(part); // Check if the part contains any of the characters +, -, *, /, or =
}



  function shuffleArray(array) {
    for (let i = array.length - 1; i > 0; i--) {
      const j = Math.floor(Math.random() * (i + 1));
      [array[i], array[j]] = [array[j], array[i]];
    }
  }

  function dragStart(event) {
    event.dataTransfer.setData('text/plain', event.target.dataset.value);
  }


  function moveAnswerElement(touchPosition) {
    currentDraggedElement.style.left = touchPosition.x - currentDraggedElement.offsetWidth / 2 + "px";
    currentDraggedElement.style.top = touchPosition.y - currentDraggedElement.offsetHeight / 2 + "px";
  }

  function touchStart(event) {
    event.preventDefault();
    const touchPosition = getTouchPosition(event);
    const answerElement = event.target;
    const answerValue = answerElement.getAttribute('data-value');

    answerElement.style.transform = "scale(1.02)"; // Optional: Add a visual feedback for touch
    answerElement.classList.add("dragging");

    touchStartPosition.x = touchPosition.x;
    touchStartPosition.y = touchPosition.y;
    currentDraggedElement = answerElement;

    // Attach touchmove and touchend listeners to the answer container
    answerContainer.addEventListener("touchmove", touchMove);
    answerContainer.addEventListener("touchend", touchEnd);
  }

  function touchMove(event) {
    event.preventDefault();
    if (!currentDraggedElement) return; // Ignore if no element is being dragged

    const touchPosition = getTouchPosition(event);
    const deltaX = touchPosition.x - touchStartPosition.x;
    const deltaY = touchPosition.y - touchStartPosition.y;
    moveAnswerElement(touchPosition);
    currentDraggedElement.style.transform = "translate(" + deltaX + "px, " + deltaY + "px) scale(1.2)";
  }

  function touchEnd(event) {
    if (!currentDraggedElement) return; // Ignore if no element is being dragged

    currentDraggedElement.classList.remove("dragging");
    currentDraggedElement.style.transform = '';
    const dropField = findDropFieldUnderPoint(event.changedTouches[0].clientX, event.changedTouches[0].clientY);
    handleDrop(currentDraggedElement, dropField);

    // Reset the currently dragged element after handling the drop
    currentDraggedElement = null;

        answerContainer.removeEventListener("touchmove", touchMove);
    answerContainer.removeEventListener("touchend", touchEnd);
  }

  function findDropFieldUnderPoint(x, y) {
    const elements = document.elementsFromPoint(x, y);
    for (const element of elements) {
      if (element.classList.contains('drop-field')) {
        return element;
      }
    }
    return null;
  }

  function animateBrokenHeart() {
  const tryLeftElementRect = tryLeftElement.getBoundingClientRect();
  const brokenHeart = document.createElement('span');
  brokenHeart.innerHTML = 'üíî';
  brokenHeart.classList.add('broken-heart');

  // Position the broken heart relative to the tryleft heart
  brokenHeart.style.left = tryLeftElementRect.left + 'px';
  brokenHeart.style.top = tryLeftElementRect.top + 'px';

  document.body.appendChild(brokenHeart);

  setTimeout(() => {
    document.body.removeChild(brokenHeart);
  }, 1000);
}


  function handleDrop(draggableAnswer, dropField) {
    if (dropField) {
      const answerValue = draggableAnswer.getAttribute('data-value');
      const dropValue = dropField.getAttribute('data-answer');
      const isCorrect = answerValue === dropValue;

      if (isCorrect) {
        playSound(matchSound);
        dropField.textContent = answerValue;
        dropField.style.background = 'palegreen';
        correctAnswersCount++;

        draggableAnswer.remove();

        if (correctAnswersCount === levels[currentLevel].questions.length) {
          setTimeout(() => {
            answerContainer.innerHTML = '';
            nextLevelButton.style.display = 'block';
          }, 200);
        }
      } else {
        playSound(nonMatchSound);
        draggableAnswer.classList.add('shake');

        setTimeout(() => {
          draggableAnswer.classList.remove('shake');
                       animateBrokenHeart();
          triesRemaining--;

          if (triesRemaining === 0) {
            // Remove all the question options from the answer container
            answerContainer.innerHTML = '';

            // Show the "Try Again" button
            tryAgainButton.style.display = 'block';

            // Hide the hearts
            tryLeftElement.textContent = '';

          } else {
            updateTries();
          }
        }, 500);
      }
    }
  }

  function tryAgain() {
    triesRemaining = 3;
    updateTries();
    tryAgainButton.style.display = 'none';
    nextLevelButton.style.display = 'none';
    currentLevel = 0;
    updateLevelText();
    initLevel();
  }

  tryAgainButton.addEventListener('click', tryAgain);
  nextLevelButton.addEventListener('click', goToNextLevel);

  function updateLevelText() {
    levelTextElement.textContent = `Level - ${currentLevel + 1}`;
  }
    // Function to update the number of tries left
  function updateTries() {
    tryLeftElement.textContent = '‚ù§'.repeat(triesRemaining);
  }

  function goToNextLevel() {
    currentLevel++;
    if (currentLevel < levels.length) {
      // Hide the "Next Level" button
      nextLevelButton.style.display = 'none';
       updateLevelText(); // Update the level text with the current level number
      initLevel();
    } else {
      alert('You completed all levels!');
    }
  }

  nextLevelButton.addEventListener('click', goToNextLevel);
  function dragEnd(event) {
    const answerElement = event.target;
    const dropField = findDropFieldUnderPoint(event.clientX, event.clientY);
    handleDrop(answerElement, dropField);

    // Reset the currently dragged element after handling the drop
    currentDraggedElement = null;
  }

  answerContainer.addEventListener('touchmove', touchMove);
  answerContainer.addEventListener('touchstart', touchStart);
  answerContainer.addEventListener('touchend', touchEnd);

 // Add the dragend event listener to the answer container for mouse devices
  answerContainer.addEventListener('dragend', dragEnd);

  // Initialize the first level and update the level text
  updateLevelText();
  initLevel();
  updateTries();
  function playSound(audio) {
    audio.currentTime = 0; // Reset the audio to the beginning
    audio.play();
  }

});

